So friends, ICC Lombard General
Insurance Company Limited has disclosed the company's numbers,
so let's see
what's in the quarter's numbers
because a little earlier ICC
Prudential also disclosed its company numbers,
so let's first look at these numbers, and
then see what the numbers are when compared. The
database is
given at the end, I will convert it into a cross and
make it, how it has been done.
Talking about the last quarter, the
company's total revenue in the last quarter was approximately
around Rs 52255 crore, you had Rs
3978 crore last year, whereas if we look at it now, the company's
revenue is around Rs 4000538 crore, so if we look at the
salt, then indirectly there is an
increase of around 15% in salt year to year, but
if we go quarter to quarter, then
you are also seeing a decline of around 15% quarter to quarter, so you are seeing the
company's revenue giving you quarter to quarter,
but if we
go year to year, then you are also seeing the company's year to year
telling you,
this company  Let's see the explanation of what the
company has done. Let's check what the company has done. If we
talk about the last quarter, then in the last quarter the
company had a profit of Rs. 3976 crores,
last year it was Rs. 3061 crores,
whereas in this quarter the company's profit is around Rs. 4206 crores. So, there is a
little problem here. What
I
told you is that the company's
revenue has fallen by 15% quarterly, but when we look at the company's
losses, on the contrary, here the
company's expenses are shown to you,
which according to me is a
little negative. Let's see
what the overall profit of the company is.
First let's see the operating profit,
after that let's see the overall profit. So, let's
talk about the operating profit of the company.
In the last quarter, the operating profit of the company can be
said to be around Rs.
1278 crores, last year the
profit was Rs. 30016 crores, whereas if we look at it now, the
profit of the company is around Rs. 331 crores. So, if we add salt to it, then
even today the
profit of the company is shown to you by
5%.  There is a jump of around Rs. 100 crore
but if we go to Quanto, there is
a huge decline in the company profit quarterly,
you will see a huge decline, you will see a huge decline of around 70%,
let us also see
what the net profit of the company comes out to be, if we
talk about the past, then the
net profit of the company in the last quarter
is now around Rs. 436 crore,
last year Rs. 349 crore, whereas in this quarter the
company has around Rs. 390 crore,
so there is a
significant decline in the net profit of Rs. 100 crore, whereas if we go from year to year,
there is a rise of around 15%, let us
also see what has happened,
although here the company has mentioned the
gross on pay net, the area of ​​MP has been
kept black by the company here,
so it is a little difficult to tell here, let us
talk about EPF in the grocery sector,
last quarter it was 8.90, last year
7.1, right now it is around 7.95, so
see the quarterly numbers a
little  Less than what has been seen because not only the
revenue of the company has fallen but the
profit of the company has also fallen but if we
look at the pulses then there are good numbers, the performance is good year after year
but overall if we
conclude then according to me it is mixed, I would
say neutral type because
if the
numbers are flat as per the quarterly fall then let's see
how the market will adjust but according to me it should be 20
percent up or the other day after tomorrow it should be down, nothing more than this so that's all
for today, if you like the video then like it and also
subscribe to my channel,
thank you.